{
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "In which year, National Games was held in Assam",
        "options": [
          "A. 2002",
          "B. 2004",
          "C. 2005",
          "D. 2007"
        ],
        "answer": "D. 2007"
      },
      {
        "question": "Gibbon Wildlife Sanctuary is located at",
        "options": [
          "A. Chirang",
          "B. Dibrugarh",
          "C. Kokrajhar",
          "D. Jorhat"
        ],
        "answer": "D. Jorhat"
      },
      {
        "question": "The Guwahati Tea Auction Centre was established in the year",
        "options": [
          "A. 1970",
          "B. 1972",
          "C. 1975",
          "D. 1977"
        ],
        "answer": "A. 1970"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which town is also known as the Manchester of Assam",
        "options": [
          "A. Jorhat",
          "B. Sualkuchi",
          "C. Diphu",
          "D. Digboi"
        ],
        "answer": "B. Sualkuchi"
      },
      {
        "question": "The Brahmaputra Cracker and Polymer Limited Industry is located at",
        "options": [
          "A. Makum",
          "B. Mariani",
          "C. Lepetkata",
          "D. Nagaon"
        ],
        "answer": "C. Lepetkata"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which city of Assam has the largest dry fish market of Asia",
        "options": [
          "A. Tangla",
          "B. Jagirod",
          "C. Dhuburi",
          "D. Tinsukia"
        ],
        "answer": "B. Jagirod"
      },
      {
        "question": "Guwahati University was established in the year",
        "options": [
          "A. 1935",
          "B. 1942",
          "C. 1948",
          "D. 1950"
        ],
        "answer": "C. 1948"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the first vice-chancellor of Guwahati University",
        "options": [
          "A. Krishna Kanta Handique",
          "B. Hemchandra Goswami",
          "C. Padmanath Gohain Baruah",
          "D. Rajanikanta Bordoloi"
        ],
        "answer": "A. Krishna Kanta Handique"
      },
      {
        "question": "Total number of Parliamentary constituency in Assam",
        "options": [
          "A. 12",
          "B. 13",
          "C. 14",
          "D. 16"
        ],
        "answer": "C. 14"
      },
      {
        "question": "\"Sheelabhadra\" was the pen name of which famous Assamese writer",
        "options": [
          "A. Syed Abdul Malik",
          "B. Satyanath Bora",
          "C. Birendra Kumar Bhattacharya",
          "D. Rebati Mohan Dutta Choudhury"
        ],
        "answer": "D. Rebati Mohan Dutta Choudhury"
      },
      {
        "question": "Namghosa was written by",
        "options": [
          "A. Sankardev",
          "B. Madhabdev",
          "C. Madhava Kandali",
          "D. None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "B. Madhabdev"
      },
      {
        "question": "\"Halodhia Choraye Baodhan Khai\" won the National Film Award for Best Feature Film in the year",
        "options": [
          "A. 1985",
          "B. 1988",
          "C. 1990",
          "D. 1991"
        ],
        "answer": "B. 1988"
      },
      {
        "question": "The film \"Halodhia Choraye Baodhan Khai\" was directed by",
        "options": [
          "A. Bhabendra Nath Saikia",
          "B. Jahnu Barua",
          "C. Bhupen Hazarika",
          "D. Manju Borah"
        ],
        "answer": "B. Jahnu Barua"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much percent of the Indian landmass is covered by the State of Assam",
        "options": [
          "A. 3.39%",
          "B. 2.39%",
          "C. 4.39%",
          "D. 2.93%"
        ],
        "answer": "B. 2.39%"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which language is used by Sankardev to write Borgeets",
        "options": [
          "A. Assamese",
          "B. Sanskrit",
          "C. Bengali",
          "D. Brajavali"
        ],
        "answer": "D. Brajavali"
      }
    ]
  }
  